<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15"?>
<devlog>
  <release name="1.6" status="open">
    <bugfix date="2002-12-02" author="o_rossmueller">
      Set correct content type for streamed resources.
    </bugfix>
    <feature group="runner">
      JUnitEE servlet provides threaded mode for long running tests. This avoids timeouts and gives the possibility to stop
      test execution. Also included is JUnitEEThreadedServlet which has threaded mode on by default.
    </feature>
    <feature group="ant">
      juniteewar task now extends the Ant war task and therefore inherits all it's features
    </feature>
    <feature group="ant">
      junitee task supports all relevant features of the junit task (formatters, if/unless conditions for test execution, stack trace filtering)
    </feature>
    <enhancement date="2002-11-03" author="o_rossmueller">
      It is now possible to force the test runner to fork a new thread by setting <code>thread=true</code> to avoid timeouts for
      long-running tests. Added JUnitEEThreadedServlet which has thread=true by default.
    </enhancement>
    <refactoring date="2002-11-03" author="o_rossmueller">
      Splitted output producer in model and render part.
    </refactoring>
    <enhancement date="2002-11-03" author="o_rossmueller">
      JUnitEEServlet produces filtered stack traces by default, filtering can be disabled by setting <code>filterTrace=false</code>
    </enhancement>
    <enhancement date="2002-11-03" author="o_rossmueller">
      Nested <code>formatter</code> elements for ant task and test element. <code>filtertrace</code> attribute for task and test.
    </enhancement>
    <bugfix date="2002-11-02" author="o_rossmueller">
      result.jsp of the example web application works with renamed EJB
    </bugfix>
    <enhancement date="2002-11-02" author="o_rossmueller">
      Added security section to the user guide.
    </enhancement>
    <enhancement date="2002-11-02" author="o_rossmueller">
      Added attribute <code>servletclass</code> to JUnitEE war task to specify the servlet class for the generated
      deployment descriptor.
    </enhancement>
    <refactoring date="2002-11-02" author="o_rossmueller">
      JUnitEE war task is now a subclass of the ant war task and therefore inherits all it's features
    </refactoring>
  </release>
</devlog>